ILR School Announcement Catalogs /3045
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Announcement Catalogs
1945-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3045
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Announcements of the the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University.
7924605
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 29, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 08, 2015
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of announcements of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University from 1945 through 1980, as well as announcements of summer and other special sessions.
Cornell University Announcements provided information of interest to prospective students, and the respective colleges comprising the university also produced announcements with more specific information regarding course offerings and degree requirements.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Public relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
7924605
- Announcement catalogs, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Announcement catalogs, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Announcement catalogs, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Announcement catalogs, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Announcement catalogs, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Announcement catalogs, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Announcement catalogs, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Announcement catalogs, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Announcement catalogs, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Announcement catalogs, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Announcement catalogs, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Announcement catalogs, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Announcement catalogs, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Announcement catalogs, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Announcement catalogs, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Announcement catalogs, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Announcement catalogs, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Announcement catalogs, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Announcement catalogs, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Announcement catalogs, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Announcement catalogs, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Announcement catalogs, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Announcement catalogs, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Announcement catalogs, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Announcement catalogs, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Announcement catalogs, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Announcement catalogs, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Announcement catalogs, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Announcement catalogs, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Announcement catalogs, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Announcement catalogs, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Announcement catalogs, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Miscellany, summer sessions and seminars, 1952-1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)